Finding Aid for Leonard Bernard Willeke papers, 1900-1984
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Professional Papers
  - Commissions
    - By Date
      - Speculative Residence, 2490 Edison Avenue, Detroit 1921 (Box 5)
        (#190)
      - Speculative Residence, 1015 Buckingham Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1921 (Box 5)
        (Commission #191)
      - Elizabeth B. Meiners, Architectural Drawings, 443 Riddle Road, Cincinnati 1921 (Map-case 3, Folder 13)
      - Speculative Residence, 938 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1922 (Box 5)
        (Commission #192)
      - Speculative Residence, 1103 Berkshire Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1922 (Box 5)
        (Commission #193)
      - George J. Zimmerman, Architectural Drawings, 1030 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1922 (Map-case 3, Folder 14)
      - Leonard B. Willeke Residence, 1100 Berkshire Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1922-1970
        (#214)
        - Correspondence and other working files, 5 folders (Box 5)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 2)
        - Architectural Drawings 1929-1930 (Map-case 3, Folder 19)
          (blueprints and original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - Wind Pointe Subdivision Homes for Charles. A. Thompson, Lincoln Park 1923-1947 (Box 5)
      - Speculative Residence, 1176 Berkshire Road, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #201)
        - Photograph and rendering 1923 (Box 5)
        - Architectural Drawings 1923 (Box 10)
      - Speculative Residence, 1068 Berkshire Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1923 (Box 5)
        (Commission #202)
      - Speculative Residence, 785 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1923 (Box 5)
      - Cincinnati Doctors' Building Company, south side of 8th between Vine and Rose 1923 (Box 5)
      - Oscar Webber Country House, Architectural Drawings circa 1921 (Map-case 8, Folder 49)
        (Commission #208)
        (original ink on tracing paper drawings and mounted renderings)
      - Oscar Webber Residence, 619 Lake Shore Road, Grosse Pointe Shores
        (Commission #217)
        - Architectural Drawings undated, 5 folders
          (original pencil drawings, blueprints, and mounted renderings)
          - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 8, Folder 50)
          - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 8, Folder 51)
            (continued)
          - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 8, Folder 52)
          - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 8, Folder 53)
          - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 8, Folder 54)
        - Planting Plans undated (Tube 24)
        - Ornamental Detail, original pencil on tracing paper drawing (Tube 25)
        - Proposed Residence for Grosse Pointe Park 1921-1924 (Box 5)
        - Correspondence 1922-1930, 4 folders (Box 5)
        - Cost Estimates 1923-1927, 3 folders (Box 5)
        - Project Accounts 1924-1928 (Box 5)
        - Specifications 1924 (Box 5)
        - Detroit City Gas Company 1924-1929 (Box 5)
        - Sewer test and lack survey 1925 (Box 5)
        - Green House 1926-1931 (Box 5)
        - Rose Garden 1926-1927 (Box 5)
        - Swimming Pool 1927-1929 (Box 5)
        - Tennis Courts 1930-1931 (Box 5)
        - Photographs, undated, 2 photographs (Box 5)
      - M.U. Burnham Estate, Green Hills and Far Hills Subdivision, Cincinnati
        - Paper records 1923-1925 (Box 5)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 3, Folder 15)
      - Speculative Residence, 1068 Berkshire Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1925 (Box 5)
      - Frederick Baker Residence, 1359 Berkshire 1925 (Box 5)
      - Roscoe B. Jackson Residence, Library Carvings 1925 (Box 5)
      - 635 East Grand Boulevard, Detroit 7 1925-1946, 2 folders (Box 5)
        (includes correspondence with Ray Meiners, the owner of the house and Willeke's brother-in-law)
      - Speculative Residence, 746 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1925 (Box 5)
        (Commission #206)
      - Charles A. Thompson Residence, 832 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #207)
        - Cost Estimates 1925 (Box 5)
        - Rendering 1925 (Box 5)
      - Chester A. Souther Residence, 19551 Burlington Drive, Detroit
        (Commission #215)
        - Paper Records 1925 (Box 5)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 3, Folder 16)
      - George E. Quigley Residence, 18634 Parkside, Detroit 1925 (Box 5)
        (Commission #209)
      - Arthur L. Wayne Residence, 17515 Wildmere Avenue, Detroit
        (Commission #218)
        - Paper Records 1925-1926 (Box 5)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 3, Folder 17)
      - William A. Petzold Residence and Garden, 1010 Three Mile Drive, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #219)
        - Photographs, 1927 (Box 5)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 3, Folder 18)
          (original pencil on tissue paper drawings)
      - Harry J. Stoops Garage, Greenhouse and Garden, 745 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1927 (Box 5)
        (Commission #223)
      - Walter V. Hemel Residence, 766 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1928-1929 (Box 5)
        (Commission #221)
      - Speculative Residence, Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1928 (Box 5)
      - Additions to J.L. Hudson Company Store, Architectural Drawings, Woodward Avenue, Detroit 1928 (Map-case 4, Folder 20)
      - John G. Rumney Landscape Plan, 17400 Jefferson Avenue, Grosse Pointe Village 1929 (Box 10)
      - Raymond J. Purdy Residence and Garden, 1012 Three Mile Drive, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #225)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 4, Folder 21)
        - Photographs 1929 (Box 5)
        - Correspondence 1929-1931, 2 folders (Box 5)
        - Cost Estimates 1929-1930 (Box 6)
        - Specifications 1929 (Box 6)
      - Wheatley Chimney Tops for the Pursell Company, Architectural drawings, Cincinnati 1930 (Tube 4)
      - French Mortgage and Bond Company Office, Alternations, 5 Larned Street, Detroit
        - Paper Records 1930, 2 folders (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings 1930 (Map-case 4, Folder 22)
      - Clarence A. Johannigman, Residence and Garden, 454Wood Avenue, Cincinnati
        - Paper Records 1933-1935, 2 folders (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 3)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 4, Folder 23)
      - A.H. Dillman Residence, Additions, Lakeville Road, Rochester, Michigan
        (Commission #226)
        - Photograph 1934 (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 4, Folder 24)
      - Henry C. Bogle Residence and Grounds, 433 Lakeland Avenue, Grosse Pointe
        (Commission #227)
        - Paper Records 1934, 2 folders (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 4)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 4, Folder 25)
          (blueprints and original pencil on tracing papers drawings)
      - Speculative Residence for Henrietta W. Boggess, 195 McKinley Road, Grosse Pointe Farms 1934 (Box 6)
        (Commission #229)
      - Zenith Carburetor Company, Alternations, 696 Hart Avenue
        (Commission #230)
        - Paper Records 1935, 2 folders (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 11)
          (blueprints and original ink and pencil drawing)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 12)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 13)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 14)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 15)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 16)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 17)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 18)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 19)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 20)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 21)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 22)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 23)
      - Henrietta W. Boggess Residence, 1251 Harvard Road, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #232)
        - Paper Records 1935 (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 2)
      - Henry B. Joy, Jr. Residence, Architectural Drawings, Grosse Pointe Farms 1935 (Box 10)
      - Madeline D. Meier Residence, 1036 Berkshire Road, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #234)
        - Sketches and Renderings 1936 (Box 6)
        - Photographs 1936 (Box 6)
        - Specifications 1936 (Box 6)
      - Speculative Residence for John H. French, 1027 Buckingham Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1936 (Box 6)
        (Commission #235 and 236)
      - Pierre V. Heftler Residence, 1154 Grayton Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1936 (Box 6)
        (Commission #236)
      - Henrietta W. Boggess Residence, 563 Fisher Road, Grosse Point
        (Commission #237)
        - Photographs, 1936 (Box 6)
        - Specifications 1936 (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 4, Folder 26)
          (blueprints, original pencil on drawing, and mounted rendering)
      - Karl F. Oehler Residence, 19740 Canterbury Road, Detroit
        (Commission #239)
        - Photographs, 1936 (Box 6)
        - Specifications 1936 (Box 6)
        - Architectural drawings undated (Map-case 5, Folder 27)
        - Architectural drawings undated (Tube 4)
      - Henry W. Axeford Farm Alterations and Additions, Architectural Drawings, Lakeville Road at Gunn Road, Rochester 1937 (Map-case 5, Folder 28)
      - William C. Oddy Residence and Garden, 806 Three Mile Drive, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #240)
        - Photographs, 1937-1938 (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings 1937, 2 mounted renderings (Box 10)
      - George F. Mehling Residence, 1142 Audubon Avenue, Grosse Pointe Park 1937 (Box 6)
        (Commission #243)
      - Henry C. Bogle, Four-family terrace, 500-506 Neff Road, Grosse Pointe 1937 (Box 6)
      - Elmer F. Ryan Residence, 18092 Birchcrest Drive, Detroit 1937 (Box 6)
        (Commission #244)
      - Victor R. Heftler Residence, Alterations to sunroom windows, 1051 Berkshire Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1937 (Box 6)
      - Proposed Residence at Grosse Pointe Park, Plan B 1937 (Box 6)
      - Lewis E. Marie School, Proposed Improvements, Cadieux Road near Kercheval, Grosse Pointe 1937 (Box 6)
      - Leonard B. Willeke Residence, 1142 Bishop Road, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #245)
        - Photographs, 1938 (Box 6)
        - Specification 1938 (Box 6)
        - Project Files 1938-1981 (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 5, Folder 29)
          (blueprints, original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - Robert M. Olp Residence, 1011 Harvard Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1938 (Box 6)
      - Pauline P. Brambett Residence, Lochmoor Drive, Grosse Pointe Woods 1939 (Box 6)
      - A.F. Walther Residence, Burns Avenue at Warren Avenue, Detroit 1939 (Box 6)
        (Commission #248)
      - Dr. F.W. Munro, Additions to Office, 16840 Kercheval Avenue, Grosse Pointe 1939-1940, 2 folders (Box 6)
        (Commission #250)
      - Elmer Ryan Store, Fire Repairs, 11738 Dexter Boulevard, Detroit 1939-1940, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Speculative Residence, Architectural Drawings, blueprint and mounted rendering, corner of Cadieux and St. Paul, Grosse Pointe 1940 (Box 10)
        (Commission #252)
      - Proposed Group of Houses for LBW, Inc., Detroit circa 1940s (Box 10)
      - Ralph H. Booth Rose Garden and Terrace, 315 Washington Road, Grosse Pointe
        - Paper Records 1940-1941 (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 5, Folder 30)
          (blueprints, original pencil drawings)
      - Adolph G. Knorpp Residence, 514 Barrington Road, Grosse Pointe Park
        - Specifications 1941 (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 5, Folder 31)
      - Lakemoor Subdivision, 741 Lakeshore Road, Grosse Pointe Shores 1941 (Box 6)
      - Victor R. Heftler Residence, 1133 Harvard Road, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #256)
        - Paper Records 1941 (Box 6)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 5, Folder 32)
      - David L. Warenta Residence, 687 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1941 (Box 6)
        (Commission #258)
      - Henry Huvaere Subdivision, Grosse Pointe Park 1944 (Box 6)
      - John Johannigman Residence, first floor alterations, 481 Riddle Road, Cincinnati 1944-1945 (Box 6)
      - Charles S. Youngman Residence, 18100 Chandler Park Drive, Detroit 1945, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Lee Terrace, Vernier Road, Grosse Pointe Woods
        (Commission #266)
        - Paper Documents 1946, 3 folders (Box 7)
        - Architectural Drawings (blueprints) undated (Tube 5)
        - Mounted Renderings undated (Box 10)
      - Clarence J. Blum Residence, Park Lane, Grosse Pointe Park 1947 (Box 7)
      - Store for Jack Chyz, Detroit 1947 (Box 7)
      - Robert K. Oddy Residence, 4526 Grayton Road, Grosse Pointe Park
        (Commission #268)
        - Paper Records 1948-1949, 4 folders (Box 7)
        - Architectural Drawings undated (Tube 2)
      - Harold Giller Residence, Windmill Pointe Subdivision, Lot 566, Grosse Pointe Park 1949 (Box 7)
      - Raymond H. Wilson Residence, 240 Stephens Road, Grosse Pointe Farms 1950-1951, 4 folders (Box 7)
      - Irving Long Residence, Porch Addition, 50 Renaud Road, Grosse Pointe Shores 1950 (Box 7)
      - Lee Court Subdivision, Verneir Road, Grosse Pointe Woods
        (Commission #270-271)
        - Paper Documents 1950-1956, 6 folders (Box 7)
        - Architectural Drawings (blueprints) undated (Tube 6)
      - Jack Kasab, Remodeling, 1400 Boston Blvd. 1952 (Box 7)
      - Leslie L. Alexander Residence, Alternations, 1321 Balfour Road, Grosse Pointe Park 1952 (Box 7)
      - Elizabeth B. Meiners Residence Photograph, 443 Riddle Road, Cincinnati, 1952 (Box 7)
    - Undated, arranged alphabetically
      - J. Willard Carpenter Residence, Architectural Drawings, Grosse Pointe undated (Box 10)
        (2 mounted renderings and original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - C.H. Chisholm Residence, Birchcrest Drive, Detroit undated (Box 7)
      - Albert R. Defever Residence, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 10)
        (blueprint and original pencil on tracing paper)
      - Alterations to Stanley F. Dole Residence, Architectural Drawings, 18005 Oak Drive, Detroit undated (Box 10)
      - Daniel J. Donovan, Garden Plans, Architectural Drawings, 405 Lakeland Avenue undated (Box 10)
        (blueprint, original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - Robert H. Durham Residence, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 10)
      - Richard Earhart Residence, Architectural Drawings, Grosse Pointe undated (Box 10)
        (mounted rendering, blueprint, original pencil on tracing paper drawing)
      - Edward C. Ecclestone Residence, Architectural Drawings, Grosse Pointe undated (Map-case 5, Folder 33)
      - Pierre V. Heftler, Speculative Residence, Grosse Pointe undated (Box 7)
      - Victor R. Heftler Residence, Grosse Pointe Park undated (Box 7)
      - J. Stewart Hudson Residence, Architectural Drawings, Grosse Pointe Farms undated (Map-case 5, Folder 34)
      - Mrs. A.M. Johannigman, Apartment Building, Riddle Road, Cincinnati
        - Specifications undated (Box 7)
        - Architectural Drawings (Box 10)
          (mounted rendering, blueprints, and original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - Anne Koestlin Residence, Architectural Drawings, 809 Berkshire Road, Grosse Pointe Park undated (Map-case 6, Folder 35)
        (original pencils on tracing paper drawings)
      - George E. Lackey Residence, Grosse Pointe undated (Map-case 6, Folder 36)
      - Ida F. Leithead Residence, Architectural Drawings, Detroit undated (Box 10)
        (mounted rendering)
      - Leland Hotel Alterations, Architectural Drawings, Detroit undated (Box 10)
      - Ezra W. Lockwood Residence, Architectural Drawings, Grosse Pointe undated (Map-case 6, Folder 37)
      - Carl E. Miller Planting Plan, Architectural Drawings, Alexandria, Virginia undated (Box 10)
      - Walter Millington Residence, Architectural Drawings, Detroit undated (Box 10)
        (blueprint and original pencil on tracing paper drawing)
      - A.F. Nygard Bungalow, Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 6, Folder 38)
      - Gerald E. Schroeder Residence, Architectural Drawing, Grosse Pointe undated (Box 10)
        (Blueprint)
      - Emmanuel J. Torn Residence, Architectural Drawing, Detroit undated (Box 11)
        (mounted rendering, blueprint, original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - Miss Turness Residence, Architectural Drawings, Marine City undated (Box 11)
      - Terrace for H. Van, Architectural Drawing, Grosse Pointe undated (Box 11)
        (mounted rendering, blueprints and original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - T.C. Van Degriet Residence, Detroit, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 11)
        (blueprint and original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - Leonard B. Willeke Residence, Architectural Drawing undated (Map-case 6, Folder 39)
      - Brayton William Westcott Residence, Mounted Renderings, Grosse Pointe undated (Box 11)
      - R. Nobel Wetherbee Terrace and Garden, Architectural Drawings, 17 Meadow Lane, Grosse Pointe Shores undated (Box 11)
      - Henry P. Williams Garden, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 11)
      - Frank G. Wimmer Residence, Mounted Rendering, Grosse Pointe Park undated (Box 11)
      - Mr. Woods Residence, Architectural Drawing, Barrington Rd, Grosse Pointe Park undated (Box 11)
        (mounted rendering, original pencil on tracing paper drawings)
      - Woodward Avenue Widening Project, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 11)
      - Irene and Harry Wyatt Residence, Architectural Drawings, Grosse Pointe undated (Map-case 6, Folder 40)
      - Filing Cabinet Plans undated (Map-case 6, Folder 41)
      - Ornamental detail drawing for door at Balfour Rd and Berkshire Rd home undated (Box 11)
      - Proposed Residence, Type 1A, 2A, 3A, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 11)
      - Proposed Residence at Grosse Pointe, Plan 55A, Architectural Drawing undated (Box 11)
        (blueprint and mounted rendering)
      - Proposed Residence at Grosse Pointe Park, #1, 3, 4, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 11)
      - Proposed Residences at Grosse Pointe, #51, 52, 53, 54, 56, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 11)
      - Proposed Residence at Grosse Pointe, Plan R, Architectural Drawings undated (Box 7)
      - Proposed Residence, Architectural Drawings undated (Map-case 6, Folder 42)
        (Commission #213)
      - Unidentified Residence, Architectural Drawing undated (Box 11)
        (Commission #260)
      - Unidentified Residence #1, Architectural drawings undated (Box 11)
      - Unidentified Residence #2, Architectural drawings undated (Map-case 6, Folder 43)
      - Unidentified Residential Renderings undated, 7 folders (Box 11)
  - Defense Housing
    The series Defense Housing (bulk dates 1943-1947) contains the records related to Willeke's work on three defense housing projects: Willow Run Courts, Dresden Avenue Defense Houses, and Goulburn Avenue Defense Houses. The names of the files for the Dresden and Goulburn projects reflect their original title. The series includes correspondence, land deeds, financial records, and architectural drawings.
    - Willow Run Courts, Washburn Highway, Allen Park, Michigan 1943
      - Cost estimates, etc. (Box 7)
      - Architectural Drawings, blueprints and six mounted renderings 1943 (Box 10)
    - Dresden Avenue Defense Houses, Detroit
      - Architectural drawings (blueprints) undated (Tube 7)
      - Architectural drawings (blueprints) undated (Tube 8)
      - Building Permits 1943-1944 (Box 7)
      - Checking Account 1943-1948, 3 folders (Box 8)
      - Chyz, Jack 1943-1945 (Box 8)
        (carpentry work correspondence and bills)
      - Defense Housing Projects Account Notebook
        - 1943-1944 (Box 8)
        - 1944-1947 (Box 8)
      - Federal Housing Administration
        - Correspondence 1942-1944, 2 folders (Box 8)
        - "Property Standards" Booklet 1940 (Box 8)
      - Frank Krue & Company
        - Bills and Receipts 1943-1944 (Box 8)
        - General Correspondence 1943-1948 (Box 8)
        - Temporary mortgages 1944 (Box 8)
        - Amortization Schedule 1944-1948, 2 folders (Box 8)
        - Final mortgages 1944 (Box 8)
      - Heftler, Pierre V. 1942-1943 (Box 8)
        (real estate)
      - Houses Sold
        - To mortgages 1944, 2 folders (Box 8)
        - Completed deeds 1944-1946, 5 folders (Box 8)
        - Contract 1947 (Box 8)
      - Houseman Spitzley Corporation
        - Tax Bills 1942-1944 (Box 8)
        - Lots 1943-1944 (Box 8)
      - Insurance
        - Final policies 1945-1947 (Box 8)
        - Wilson 1945-1955 (Box 8)
      - McGiverin, Dorothy
        (land owner)
        - Correspondence and Warranty Deed 1943 (Box 8)
        - Tax Bills 1943-1944 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous 1944-1945 (Box 9)
        (correspondence and receipts)
      - Nash, Frederick 1943-1945 (Box 9)
      - Photographs, 1943 (Box 9)
      - Turner and Wilson 1944 (Box 9)
        (realtors)
      - Waivers of Lien 1944 (Box 9)
      - War Production Board Correspondence 1942-1943 (Box 9)
    - Goulburn Avenue Defense Houses, Detroit
      - Architectural drawings undated (Tube 9)
      - Architectural drawings undated (Tube 10)
      - Agreements Sellings 1942 (Box 9)
      - Associates Discount Corporation 1942-1943 (Box 9)
        (voucher receipts)
      - Bodman, Longley, Bogle, Middleton, and Armstrong, attorneys 1945 (Box 9)
      - Building Permits 1943-1944 (Box 9)
      - Checking Accounts 1945-1947 (Box 9)
      - Christine Daniel 1944-1945 (Box 9)
      - Domenic Cornacchia 1942-1943 (Box 9)
        (excavation work correspondence and bills)
      - Emeric Baret 1942-1946 (Box 9)
        (mason contractor)
      - Fort Wayne Mortgage Company 1946 (Box 9)
      - Frank Krue & Company
        (mortgage company)
        - General Correspondence 1942-1949, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - Invoices 1942-1944 (Box 9)
        - Settlement Sheets 1942-1943 (Box 9)
        - Mortgage Amortization Schedule 1943-1947 (Box 9)
        - Bills and Receipts 1945-1955 (Box 9)
      - Houses Sold
        - Agreements 1943-1945 (Box 9)
        - Cash to mortgage 1944 (Box 9)
        - Turner, Wilson and Sparks 1946 (Box 9)
      - Insurance
        - Completed and all others 1943-1945, 3 folders (Box 9)
        - Final policies 1946-1947 (Box 9)
      - Melvin F. Lanphar and Company 1943-1946 (Box 9)
        (mortgages and realty insurance)
      - L.B.W., Inc. (all construction cancelled checks) 1943 (Box 9)
      - Lot 64, Josephine Grima 1945-1949 (Box 9)
      - Lot 1746 Charles Olechowski (mortgage papers) 1946-1951 (Box 9)
      - Lot 1747 Mitford Mortgage Papers 1947-1955 (Box 9)
      - Lot 1761 Tweedle Mortgage Papers 1946-1966 (Box 9)
      - Photographs, 1943 (Box 9)
      - Pieschke, Bob (correspondence, bills, etc.) 1956-1961 (Box 9)
      - Quinlan, John 1943-1946 (Box 9)
        (Houseman Spitzley Corporation)
      - Rejected and Void deals 1943-1945 (Box 9)
      - Rental and Sales Department Notebook 1943-1945 (Box 9)
      - Sub-division Plates 1927 (Box 9)
      - Turner, Wilson and Sparks 1943-1944 (Box 9)